[
  {
    "question": "(m + 2)(m - 2)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 7)(a - 7)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 7)(n - 7)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 2)(n - 2)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 4)(m - 4)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 7)(m - 7)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 5)(c - 5)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 3)(n - 3)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 7)(b - 7)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 6)(x - 6)",
    "answer": "x^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6)(b - 6)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 9)(n - 9)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 4)(b - 4)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 1)(m - 1)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 9)(q - 9)",
    "answer": "q^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 6)(m - 6)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 8)(c - 8)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3)(a - 3)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 4)(b - 4)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 5)(a - 5)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 9)(c - 9)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 7)(y - 7)",
    "answer": "y^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 9)(m - 9)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 2)(x - 2)",
    "answer": "x^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 1)(a - 1)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 6)(p - 6)",
    "answer": "p^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 6)(n - 6)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 2)(q - 2)",
    "answer": "q^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 6)(p - 6)",
    "answer": "p^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 6)(n - 6)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 3)(b - 3)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 4)(p - 4)",
    "answer": "p^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 2)(b - 2)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 1)(c - 1)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 5)(m - 5)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 7)(a - 7)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 1)(c - 1)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 1)(a - 1)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 6)(n - 6)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 9)(m - 9)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 8)(n - 8)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 1)(b - 1)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(y + 9)(y - 9)",
    "answer": "y^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3)(a - 3)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 1)(m - 1)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 9)(a - 9)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 7)(m - 7)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 4)(c - 4)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 7)(n - 7)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 8)(a - 8)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 8q)(n - 8q)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 64q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 3m)(a - 3m)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 9m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 7z)(b - 7z)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 49z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 3z)(b - 3z)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 9z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 5z)(c - 5z)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 25z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 2y)(b - 2y)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 4y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 5z)(n - 5z)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 25z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 6x)(a - 6x)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + n)(b - n)",
    "answer": "b^2 - n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 4z)(b - 4z)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 16z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 6y)(a - 6y)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 4x)(b - 4x)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 16x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 6p)(m - 6p)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 36p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6y)(b - 6y)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 5n)(m - 5n)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 25n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 7n)(b - 7n)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 49n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 6z)(x - 6z)",
    "answer": "x^2 - 36z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + q)(a - q)",
    "answer": "a^2 - q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 8y)(x - 8y)",
    "answer": "x^2 - 64y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 7p)(a - 7p)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 49p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + z)(q - z)",
    "answer": "q^2 - z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 8x)(a - 8x)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 64x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 5p)(b - 5p)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 25p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(n + 7y)(n - 7y)",
    "answer": "n^2 - 49y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 9z)(c - 9z)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 81z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 9q)(b - 9q)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 81q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 9q)(p - 9q)",
    "answer": "p^2 - 81q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + q)(p - q)",
    "answer": "p^2 - q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 7n)(a - 7n)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 49n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 8p)(m - 8p)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 64p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 5y)(q - 5y)",
    "answer": "q^2 - 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 9m)(c - 9m)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 81m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 8q)(a - 8q)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 64q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 5p)(m - 5p)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 25p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(p + 9y)(p - 9y)",
    "answer": "p^2 - 81y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 6c)(a - 6c)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 36c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 4p)(a - 4p)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 16p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 8n)(c - 8n)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 64n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + m)(c - m)",
    "answer": "c^2 - m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + y)(a - y)",
    "answer": "a^2 - y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 5m)(c - 5m)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 25m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6q)(b - 6q)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 36q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 7m)(c - 7m)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 49m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(c + 4p)(c - 4p)",
    "answer": "c^2 - 16p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 9y)(b - 9y)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 81y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 6p)(a - 6p)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 36p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(x + 8z)(x - 8z)",
    "answer": "x^2 - 64z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 6x)(b - 6x)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 36x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(m + 4z)(m - 4z)",
    "answer": "m^2 - 16z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(b + 2n)(b - 2n)",
    "answer": "b^2 - 4n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8m + 4)(-8m - 4)",
    "answer": "64m^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2b + 3)(2b - 3)",
    "answer": "4b^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6b + 1)(-6b - 1)",
    "answer": "36b^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 4)(a - 4)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7a + 7)(7a - 7)",
    "answer": "49a^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8n + 5)(-8n - 5)",
    "answer": "64n^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-x + 1)(-x - 1)",
    "answer": "x^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8c + 1)(-8c - 1)",
    "answer": "64c^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2n + 8)(-2n - 8)",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6a + 4)(-6a - 4)",
    "answer": "36a^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4x + 5)(4x - 5)",
    "answer": "16x^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3y + 4)(3y - 4)",
    "answer": "9y^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8p + 4)(8p - 4)",
    "answer": "64p^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4n + 8)(-4n - 8)",
    "answer": "16n^2 - 64"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 6)(3b - 6)",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c + 2)(3c - 2)",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6b + 7)(-6b - 7)",
    "answer": "36b^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7c + 5)(-7c - 5)",
    "answer": "49c^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + 9)(3p - 9)",
    "answer": "9p^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3b + 9)(-3b - 9)",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5c + 4)(-5c - 4)",
    "answer": "25c^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7b + 2)(-7b - 2)",
    "answer": "49b^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6b + 1)(-6b - 1)",
    "answer": "36b^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8a + 9)(8a - 9)",
    "answer": "64a^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-q + 3)(-q - 3)",
    "answer": "q^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3b + 9)(-3b - 9)",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5q + 6)(5q - 6)",
    "answer": "25q^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-9a + 4)(-9a - 4)",
    "answer": "81a^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7b + 1)(-7b - 1)",
    "answer": "49b^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4m + 5)(-4m - 5)",
    "answer": "16m^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3n + 7)(3n - 7)",
    "answer": "9n^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6c + 3)(6c - 3)",
    "answer": "36c^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3a + 6)(3a - 6)",
    "answer": "9a^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(a + 1)(a - 1)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 1"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4c + 5)(-4c - 5)",
    "answer": "16c^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3m + 2)(-3m - 2)",
    "answer": "9m^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2p + 3)(-2p - 3)",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5q + 5)(-5q - 5)",
    "answer": "25q^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8q + 4)(-8q - 4)",
    "answer": "64q^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4p + 3)(-4p - 3)",
    "answer": "16p^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7x + 7)(7x - 7)",
    "answer": "49x^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6p + 3)(6p - 3)",
    "answer": "36p^2 - 9"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7a + 4)(7a - 4)",
    "answer": "49a^2 - 16"
  },
  {
    "question": "(8c + 6)(8c - 6)",
    "answer": "64c^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2n + 7)(-2n - 7)",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-a + 5)(-a - 5)",
    "answer": "a^2 - 25"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5n + 2)(5n - 2)",
    "answer": "25n^2 - 4"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2a + 6)(2a - 6)",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 36"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3c + 7)(3c - 7)",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 49"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2p + 9)(-2p - 9)",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 81"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3p + x)(3p - x)",
    "answer": "9p^2 - x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6c + 5p)(-6c - 5p)",
    "answer": "36c^2 - 25p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7q + 4y)(7q - 4y)",
    "answer": "49q^2 - 16y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4n + 3q)(-4n - 3q)",
    "answer": "16n^2 - 9q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6a + 2m)(-6a - 2m)",
    "answer": "36a^2 - 4m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5c + 3q)(-5c - 3q)",
    "answer": "25c^2 - 9q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7x + 4z)(7x - 4z)",
    "answer": "49x^2 - 16z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(2p + 7x)(2p - 7x)",
    "answer": "4p^2 - 49x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6x + 5z)(-6x - 5z)",
    "answer": "36x^2 - 25z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4a + n)(4a - n)",
    "answer": "16a^2 - n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4a + 8n)(4a - 8n)",
    "answer": "16a^2 - 64n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4p + 5z)(-4p - 5z)",
    "answer": "16p^2 - 25z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4b + 2q)(4b - 2q)",
    "answer": "16b^2 - 4q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5m + 8y)(-5m - 8y)",
    "answer": "25m^2 - 64y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5n + 4x)(-5n - 4x)",
    "answer": "25n^2 - 16x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2q + 8x)(-2q - 8x)",
    "answer": "4q^2 - 64x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(9b + 7z)(9b - 7z)",
    "answer": "81b^2 - 49z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7b + 5x)(7b - 5x)",
    "answer": "49b^2 - 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7b + 8c)(7b - 8c)",
    "answer": "49b^2 - 64c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-8b + 6p)(-8b - 6p)",
    "answer": "64b^2 - 36p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5a + 2x)(-5a - 2x)",
    "answer": "25a^2 - 4x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7m + 3p)(7m - 3p)",
    "answer": "49m^2 - 9p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7m + 4p)(-7m - 4p)",
    "answer": "49m^2 - 16p^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2a + 5m)(-2a - 5m)",
    "answer": "4a^2 - 25m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6a + 7m)(-6a - 7m)",
    "answer": "36a^2 - 49m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-5y + 3z)(-5y - 3z)",
    "answer": "25y^2 - 9z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5b + 7y)(5b - 7y)",
    "answer": "25b^2 - 49y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5c + q)(5c - q)",
    "answer": "25c^2 - q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4a + b)(4a - b)",
    "answer": "16a^2 - b^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7c + 8y)(7c - 8y)",
    "answer": "49c^2 - 64y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(4c + m)(4c - m)",
    "answer": "16c^2 - m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3m + 6q)(-3m - 6q)",
    "answer": "9m^2 - 36q^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5c + 7m)(5c - 7m)",
    "answer": "25c^2 - 49m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6q + 6y)(-6q - 6y)",
    "answer": "36q^2 - 36y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3c + 5x)(-3c - 5x)",
    "answer": "9c^2 - 25x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5p + y)(5p - y)",
    "answer": "25p^2 - y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3b + 2m)(3b - 2m)",
    "answer": "9b^2 - 4m^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-3p + 9z)(-3p - 9z)",
    "answer": "9p^2 - 81z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(6a + 8z)(6a - 8z)",
    "answer": "36a^2 - 64z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(3m + 7z)(3m - 7z)",
    "answer": "9m^2 - 49z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(7m + 3x)(7m - 3x)",
    "answer": "49m^2 - 9x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4p + 8z)(-4p - 8z)",
    "answer": "16p^2 - 64z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-2n + 8x)(-2n - 8x)",
    "answer": "4n^2 - 64x^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5p + 5y)(5p - 5y)",
    "answer": "25p^2 - 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6p + 2z)(-6p - 2z)",
    "answer": "36p^2 - 4z^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(5b + 5y)(5b - 5y)",
    "answer": "25b^2 - 25y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(q + 4y)(q - 4y)",
    "answer": "q^2 - 16y^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-4a + 2c)(-4a - 2c)",
    "answer": "16a^2 - 4c^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-7b + 9n)(-7b - 9n)",
    "answer": "49b^2 - 81n^2"
  },
  {
    "question": "(-6m + 5n)(-6m - 5n)",
    "answer": "36m^2 - 25n^2"
  }
]